unomy.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy – Unomy | B2B Sales and Marketing Intelligence

Skip to content

Unomy (“Unomy” or “We”) is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to the Unomy website and users of the Unomy service (the “Service”). This privacy policy (the “Policy) was prepared because we believe you (the “User”) should know as much as possible about the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties.

Principally, Unomy uses the personal information provided by the User to operate and enable the Service, to improve and customize your experience with the Service, and to send you Service related updates, notices and announcements. We may also use that information to notify the User about our new products, services, updates and other Unomy information we think the User may find to be of interest.

In addition, this Policy describes your choices with respect to how we collect and use your information. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this Policy at any time. Your continued use of the website (the “Website”) and our services, constitute your acceptance of this Policy and any updates thereto.

We are very conscious of the User’s right to privacy regarding the information the User supplies to us. At Unomy, our policy is to use the information exclusively to provide the User with better service. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you are welcome to contact us as provided in the Contacting Us at Unomy section of this Privacy Policy.

##  1\. The Information We collect for our Service 

###  a) Aggregation of User Data 

Unomy may aggregate the information you provide with similar information collected from other visitors to the Website or users of the Service in order to evaluate or enhance the Website or its Services. Specifically, Unomy may aggregate data to determine the usage patterns or interests of visitors to the Website or users of the Service, or for purposes related to the technical support or security of the Website and our computer systems. For example, we collect traffic data that is regularly generated with Users' online activities such as IP addresses, the name of the website from which you entered our website, session durations, viewed pages, type of mobile device and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website. The aggregated data that we evaluate, contains no personal information or other information that could identify an individual. 

###  b) Usage Tracking Within The Unomy Service 

Unomy may aggregate the information you provide with similar information collected from other visitors to the Website or users of the Service in order to evaluate or enhance the Website or its Services. Specifically, Unomy may aggregate data to determine the usage patterns or interests of visitors to the Website or users of the Service, or for purposes related to the technical support or security of the Website and our computer systems. For example, we collect traffic data that is regularly generated with Users' online activities such as IP addresses, the name of the website from which you entered our website, session durations, viewed pages, type of mobile device and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website. The aggregated data that we evaluate, contains no personal information or other information that could identify an individual. 

###  c) Cookies 

Our Website uses “Cookies” to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Website correctly or at all. 

## 2\. User information to Certain Third Parties

Unomy may, on occasion, provide some general usage information from the Products to our data suppliers for royalty-related purposes. Any information that we may provide to our data suppliers contains no personal details about individual users. Additionally, no information that we collect from the Website that you provide to us is ever sold to third parties. When appropriate or required we may disclose information, including personal information, collected from the Website to protect our legal rights or in response to a court order, or in connection with a sale or merger of Unomy or its assets. Unomy will endeavor to make such disclosures subject to protective orders or confidentiality agreements. With respect to information collected in the course of our marketing activities, Unomy may exchange business leads with our affiliates from time to time. Additionally, we may, on limited occasions, share your personal information with third-party marketing partners. These partners generally consist of persons or entities with whom we maintain a relationship and which offer certain complementary products and services to those Services that we offer. We will take commercially reasonable efforts to make sure that such third parties safeguard your personal information. Further, you are permitted at any time to request that we refrain from sharing your personal information with such third parties, or that we disclose who we shared your personal information with. In order to make such requests, please follow the instructions set forth below with regard to requests made in connection with your personal information.

## 3\. Receipt of Communications

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive communications from us you may opt out by updating your Unomy account. You may still receive certain communications from us at your request or at the request of your organization.

## 4\. Server Security

The Unomy servers are physically secure and may only be accessed by Unomy’s technical or support personnel whose jobs specifically relate to maintaining the integrity of the Unomy servers or supporting product-related functions. Such individuals are required to maintain the security of the servers and the confidentiality of the information contained in the servers. Unomy takes all reasonable and appropriate steps to protect your personal information, including by encrypting such information, maintaining readily accessible steps to limit access, working to detect unauthorized access, and not storing such information any longer than we need to.

## 5\. Third Party Sites

As a visitor to the Website or a subscriber to our Services, you may decide to visit a third party’s website through links available on our Website. Although the Unomy branding may still be visible, you will be subject to that third-party’s privacy policy, if one exists. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of third-party websites you choose to visit. Unomy is not responsible for how that third-party may collect or use your personal information.

## 6\. Contacting us at Unomy

Should you have a concern about Unomy’s collection or use of your personal information, Unomy would like to hear about it – info@unomy.com.

## 7\. Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Policy so individuals are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use individual personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will post a notice on our Site or comply with other procedures as required by applicable laws.

#### Forgot your Password?

It happens.   
Enter your email address bellow and we'll send you a link to set up a new one.

#### Thank you!

One of our representatives will contact you shortly.

#### Please check your email!

We sent you a link to reset your password

#### Password reset

Your password has been successfully changed
